

District Coordinator seeking roles in Project Management, Scope Management, Technical Support, Business Management, Networking, Data Analysis, Resource Management, Application Maintenance, Vendor Management, MIS Reporting, Quality Management



Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Pune, Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science and

Engineer]

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: District Coordinator, Software Developer, Project Management, Scope Management, Technical Support, Business

Management, Networking, Data Analysis, Resource Management, Application Maintenance, Vendor Management, MIS

Reporting, Quality Management

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

A professional with over 3 years of experience in Project Coordination

Knowledge of liaising with different Departments and managing the administration work with quality

Proficient at project management activities which includes planning, design, scope management, estimation, resource administration and completion of project within specified parameters

Skilled at performing basic admin. duties including printing, sending emails, and ordering office supplies Currently pursuing Data Analysis in MS Excel from UDEMY

Work Experience

Smartchip Pvt. Ltd as District Coordinator

Nov 2017 to Dec 2020

My roles and responsibilities was coordinate with govt education department whatever requirement they need what the status of education department projects and also to provide technical support to our district manpower.

Tata ClassEdge as Edge Coordinator

Apr 2014 to May 2015

TATA CLASS EDGE is software that used for in school i was working here as a edge coordinator their my role and responsibilities was to provide training to our school staff of that software and also and troubleshooting and software updation.

L. B. D. International School as Teacher (Kota, Bilaspur)

Jul 2013 to Mar 2014

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineer) from C.S.V.T.U, Institute of Technology in 2013

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Microsoft office DATA ANALYSIS and Dashboard reporting

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
C, C++	
Windows 2000, XP, Vista	
WINDOWS 7, WINDOWS 8	
MS office,MS Excel	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

US Work Status: Authorized to Work in the US

Countries: India, Dubai, United States

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time